Comparing module AppBackgroundTask
Comparing module AppLocker
Comparing module AppvClient
Disable-Appv not found in source version, skip
Comparing module Appx
Get-AppxLastError not found in source version, skip
Comparing module AssignedAccess
Get-AssignedAccess not found in source version, skip
Comparing module BestPractices
Comparing module BitsTransfer
Comparing module BranchCache
Comparing module CimCmdlets
Comparing module ConfigCI
Get-CIPolicyInfo not found in source version, skip
Comparing module Defender
Comparing module DirectAccessClientComponents
Comparing module Dism
Comparing module DnsClient
Comparing module EventTracingManagement
Comparing module International
Get-WinAcceptLanguageFromLanguageListOptOut not found in source version, skip
Comparing module iSCSI
Comparing module IscsiTarget
Comparing module Kds
Get-KdsConfiguration not found in source version, skip
Comparing module Microsoft.PowerShell.Archive
Comparing module Microsoft.PowerShell.Diagnostics
Comparing module Microsoft.PowerShell.Host
Stop-Transcript not found in source version, skip
Comparing module Microsoft.PowerShell.LocalAccounts
Comparing module Microsoft.PowerShell.Management
Get-Transaction not found in source version, skip
Comparing module Microsoft.PowerShell.ODataUtils
Comparing module Microsoft.PowerShell.Operation.Validation
Comparing module Microsoft.PowerShell.Security
Comparing module Microsoft.PowerShell.Utility
Get-Culture not found in source version, skip
Comparing module Microsoft.WSMan.Management
Get-WSManCredSSP not found in source version, skip
Comparing module MMAgent
Comparing module MsDtc
Comparing module NetAdapter
Comparing module NetConnection
Comparing module NetEventPacketCapture
Comparing module NetLbfo
Comparing module NetNat
Comparing module NetQos
Comparing module NetSecurity
Comparing module NetSwitchTeam
Comparing module NetTCPIP
Comparing module NetworkConnectivityStatus
Comparing module NetworkSwitchManager
Comparing module NetworkTransition
Comparing module NFS
Comparing module PackageManagement
Comparing module PcsvDevice
Comparing module Pester
Comparing module PKI
Get-CertificateNotificationTask not found in source version, skip
Comparing module PlatformIdentifier
Comparing module PnpDevice
Comparing module PowerShellGet
Comparing module PrintManagement
Comparing module PSDesiredStateConfiguration
Comparing module PSDiagnostics
Comparing module PSReadline
Get-PSReadlineOption not found in source version, skip
Comparing module PSScheduledJob
Comparing module PSWorkflow
Comparing module PSWorkflowUtility
Comparing module ScheduledTasks
Comparing module SecureBoot
Confirm-SecureBootUEFI not found in source version, skip
Comparing module SecurityCmdlets
Comparing module ServerCore
Get-DisplayResolution not found in source version, skip
Comparing module ServerManager
Comparing module ServerManagerTasks
Comparing module SmbShare
Comparing module SmbWitness
Comparing module SoftwareInventoryLogging
Comparing module StartLayout
Comparing module Storage
Disable-PhysicalDiskIndication (!)
	Confirm (-)
	PassThru (-)
	WhatIf (-)


Enable-PhysicalDiskIndication (!)
	Confirm (-)
	PassThru (-)
	WhatIf (-)


Disable-PhysicalDiskIdentification (!)
	Confirm (-)
	PassThru (-)
	WhatIf (-)


Enable-PhysicalDiskIdentification (!)
	Confirm (-)
	PassThru (-)
	WhatIf (-)


Get-PhysicalDisk (!)
	InputObject (+)ThrottleLimit (-) AsJob (-)


Reset-PhysicalDisk (!)
	Confirm (-)
	PassThru (-)
	WhatIf (-)


Update-StorageFirmware (!)
	Confirm (-)
	PassThru (-)
	WhatIf (-)


Get-PhysicalExtent (+)

Get-PhysicalExtentAssociation (+)

Comparing module TLS
Comparing module TroubleshootingPack
Comparing module TrustedPlatformModule
Enable-TpmAutoProvisioning not found in source version, skip
Comparing module UEV
Disable-Uev not found in source version, skip
Comparing module UserAccessLogging
Comparing module VpnClient
Comparing module Wdac
Comparing module Whea
Comparing module WindowsDeveloperLicense
Get-WindowsDeveloperLicense not found in source version, skip
Comparing module WindowsErrorReporting
Disable-WindowsErrorReporting not found in source version, skip
Comparing module WindowsSearch
Get-WindowsSearchSetting not found in source version, skip
Comparing module WindowsUpdate
